<?xml version="1.0"?>
<houses>
    <gryffindor>
        <description>"Gryffindor values bravery, daring, nerve, and chivalry. Its emblematic animal is the lion and its colours are scarlet and gold. Minerva McGonagall is the most recent Head of Gryffindor. Sir Nicholas de Mimsy-Porpington, also known as &quot;Nearly Headless Nick&quot;, was the house ghost. The common room is located in one of the highest towers at Hogwarts, the entrance is situated on the seventh floor in the east wing of the castle and is guarded by a portrait of The Fat Lady. She permits entrance if given the correct password, which is changed numerous times throughout the school year. Famous Gryffindors include: Albus Dumbledore, Harry Potter, and Celestina Warbeck."</description>
        <description>"Gryffindors are another individualistic House, but one that&apos;s primarily defined by its daring, desire for fame, and great exploits. Per JKR, Gryffs want to be trusted and praised - but so do Ravenclaws, and in greater numbers than the Gryffs!)"</description>
        <description>"Gryffs are deeply, deeply defined by forests, and by the element of fire. Fire here is actual fire: not Hufflepuff&apos;s nurturing sunlight, but an absolutely scorching-hot flame. Fire is passion, and Gryffindors are passionate about their beliefs, and standing up for what they believe in (and, more pointedly, who they believe in: Gryffindor is an individualistic House, but it cares deeply about people - it&apos;s not cerebral in the way of Ravenclaw or Slytherin.) A Gryffindor&apos;s first impulse is always to draw their wand and act."</description>
        <description>"Gryffindors also like being around people. They&apos;re not group-focused - it&apos;s individual glory they&apos;re seeking after all - but they like being around friends, and hate being bored. (They may feel the need to make a little mischief to keep from being bored.) A Gryffindor never has to worry about being overlooked - they need to keep friends around them and are a more extroverted House on the whole, but they&apos;re generally too active to be ignored. Physical discomfort doesn&apos;t bother them at all."</description>
        <description>"Gryffindors are fully willing to bluff, but never to cheat or threaten. The founder of the house was Godric Gryffindor. Gryffindor corresponds to the element of Fire."</description>
        <description>"Gryffs do care about people, and seek external validation from others: they&apos;re very interested in proving themselves. A Gryffindor is going to be very interested in being a hero; as Hermione has said, they may have a &quot;saving-people-thing.&quot; Adventure, and more importantly action, are the traits of a Gryffindor: Gryffs want to be heroes. A willingness to confront the darkness, to fight for the underdog, to explore and defend: this is Gryffindor House."</description>
    </gryffindor> 
    <ravenclaw>
        <description>"Ravenclaw values intelligence, knowledge, and wit. Its emblematic animal is the eagle, and its colours are blue and bronze. The Ravenclaw Head of House in the 1990s was Filius Flitwick. The ghost of Ravenclaw is the Grey Lady, who was the daughter of Rowena Ravenclaw, the house&apos;s founder. Ravenclaw corresponds to the element of air. The Ravenclaw common room and dormitories are located in a tower on the west side of the castle. Ravenclaw students must answer a riddle as opposed to giving a password to enter their dormitories. This riddle, however, can be answered by non-Ravenclaws. Famous Ravenclaws include: Gilderoy Lockheart, Ignatia Wildsmith (inventor of floo powder), and Garrick Ollivander."</description>
        <description>"Ravenclaws are defined by curiosity and the love of learning, first and foremost. A Ravenclaw will always seek knowledge; they want to know the why of everything. They love learning, and will want to seek as much knowledge as possible, whenever possible, by whatever means they can - even if that may involve some risk, which &apos;Claws are normally quite averse to. Ravenclaws are readers; they love books, which they prize greatly, and have an insatiable hunger for knowledge. They like elegance, but aren&apos;t as haughty as the Slytherins can seem; if Ravenclaws become elitist, it&apos;s because they think they&apos;ve sensed stupidity or close-mindedness, not because someone isn&apos;t a member of their group. "</description>
        <description>"The unknown attracts Ravenclaws, although they can be more danger-averse than Slytherins, who value mystery even when they sense danger. Unlike Slytherins, Ravenclaws tend to focus on the future over the past: the possibilities excite a Ravenclaw, and they tend to be deeply interested in the what-ifs of a situation. Ravenclaws do care for humanity, but are generally much more cerebral or introverted than Gryffs and Puffs - Ravenclaws have no problems with being by themselves, because they can always occupy themselves with books or theories or thoughts, but when they want to talk, they&apos;ll be upset if no one listens."</description>
        <description>"Ravenclaws are the most conflict-averse of all the Houses: they tend to avoid conflict whenever possible, seeking creative solutions to avoid a fight. They would rather rely on their wits than their wands, and unlike Gryffindors, are much more likely to stop and review a situation before charging forward. They also have a strong sense of fairness in academic situations, and want recognition for themselves. Ravenclaws are free-thinkers, likely to analyze everything: they think about everything, form opinions about it, and are the most open-minded (out-there) of all the Houses. Creativity and an open mind, as much as pure intelligence, defines Ravenclaw House: &apos;Claws value their own inner world, and have too much of an imagination to ever be sad or bored just because they&apos;re alone."</description>
        <description>"Ravenclaws are also the most individualistic of all the Houses, and the most open-minded. Hufflepuff is known for its tolerance, but Ravenclaw may actually be more tolerant of people with wild ideas: when Puff practicality conflicts with high-flying Ravenclaw ideas, the Puffs may draw the line. However, where Puffs tolerate everybody, Ravenclaws have no time for stupidity or ignorance, particularly the latter. Ravenclaws despise ignorance. They&apos;re happy to help a person learn - but they have no patience with the close-minded."</description>
        <description>"Ravenclaw is associated with the element of air, which has historically been associated with thought and intellect. Ravenclaw is the House of wit, wisdom, and learning - not necessarily school-smarts, but a passion for knowledge of some kind, an open mind, and a desire to achieve. Ravenclaws are also extremely individualistic: trying to group Ravenclaws can sometimes be like herding cats (or caging eagles in flight.) Where JKR thinks Ravenclaws should fear falling from great heights, they actually fear being caged in the dark. In other words, &apos;Claws may be the strangest House, even to the creator who&apos;s trying to define them."</description>
    </ravenclaw> 
    <slytherin>
        <description>"The river in Pottermore represents unity, and Slytherin is a group-oriented House. Like Gryffindor, Slytherins are seeking individual greatness - but Slytherins look out for their own group and see themselves as much more unified than Ravenclaws or Gryffindors. However, a Slytherin&apos;s loyalty to the group only extends so far: they won&apos;t cover for someone who&apos;s overshadowing them academically, particularly when they know that&apos;s been achieved through foul play. (This is what Slyths and Puffs tend to split on: a large percentage of Slytherins do believe that group loyalty extends to covering up academic dishonesty, but JKR disagrees.)"</description>
        <description>"Slytherins care more about their reputation in the here and now; it matters even more than their achievements. It&apos;s better to be powerful in life than renowned in death, because you can reap the benefits while alive. They tend to have the most diverse problems: snakes are cold-blooded, so cold bothers them, but in a more general sense the worst thing that can happen to them is being ignored. After all, you can&apos;t be great if no one is willing to pay attention to you!"</description>
        <description>"Boredom is a large issue for Slytherins, they don&apos;t get lost as easily in their heads as Ravenclaws do, and they&apos;re only interested in learning for the sake of applied knowledge. If it&apos;s not useful, Slytherins don&apos;t want to know it. Slytherins are more interventionist and more risk-oriented than Hufflepuffs or Ravenclaws."</description>
        <description>"Slytherins are much more willing to take risks than Hufflepuffs or Ravenclaws - but where Gryffindors take risks for the greater good, or to be heroes, Slytherins are much more likely to be doing it to benefit themselves. (For example, Slytherins are more likely to want superpowers that may have great downsides, to learn a method of travel that is subtle and quiet but has the greatest risk of a life-threatening accident, or to take a mysterious potion with effects that most people hate - but only if they believe that they can achieve great personal gain by doing so.) The creatures they prefer to study are associated with one of three things: water, Darkness, or cunning."</description>
        <description>"Slytherins are cunning and confrontational - and lack a sense of fair play. They&apos;ll cheat in a fight if they can get away with it, but woe betide anyone stupid enough to get caught; they&apos;ll threaten a Muggle if they think they can. Slytherins are the only House that doesn&apos;t list trusted as their #1 value (in practice, it&apos;s their #2, with praised as their #1.) However, the values that JKR associates them with are much more explicitly negative: an ideal Slytherin would desire to be feared or envied, qualities with the most outright negative connotations. (Envy, after all, is one of the Seven Deadly Sins, and fear is obviously negative.)"</description>
        <description>"Despite being a group-oriented House, Slytherins are cerebral - they don&apos;t care so much for people, particularly people they don&apos;t know. They have no patience for incompetence in others. They enjoy elegance and refinement, along with mystery. Where Ravenclaws want to explore mysteries and shed light on them, Slytherins want to be the mystery: great and prominent, but distant from the masses. Darkness, the flip side of the coin, the dark side of the moon: all of these are very essentially Slytherin. Slytherins also are the most focused on the past and tradition. They would prefer to preserve old things rather than the new; they look to the past rather than to the future."</description>
    </slytherin>  
    <hufflepuff>
        <description>"Hufflepuff, founded by Helga Hufflepuff, values hard work, dedication, patience, loyalty, and fair play. Its emblematic animal is the badger, and Yellow and Black are its colours. Pomona Sprout was the Head of Hufflepuff during 1991 - 1998, Sprout left the post of Head of Hufflepuff and Herbology Professor sometime before 2017 and her successor for the position of Head of Hufflepuff is currently unknown. The Fat Friar is its ghost. Hufflepuff corresponds to the element of earth. The Hufflepuff dormitories and common room are located somewhere in the basement, near the castle&apos;s kitchens. It can be accessed by tapping the barrel two from the bottom, middle of the second row in the rhythm of &quot;Helga Hufflepuff&quot; and is described as being a cosy and welcoming place with yellow hangings, fat armchairs, and underground tunnels that lead to the dormitories, which have perfectly round doors, similar to barrel tops. Famous Hufflepuffs include: Hengist of Woodcroft (founder of Hogsmead), Newt Scamander, and Artemisia Lufkin (first female minister for magic)."</description>
        <description>"Hufflepuffs are defined by their love of family, comfort, and living things first and foremost. Anything involving animals or plants is going to appeal to them: Care of Magical Creatures and Herbology are subjects beloved by Hufflepuffs. They also care deeply for people and enjoy the company of others; being alone or feeling unloved are things Puffs dislike intensely. Ultimately, Hufflepuffs are interested in helping both people and animals, but are much less confrontational or daring than Gryffindors. They&apos;re the least likely to care about individual achievement or House points, and most likely to focus on their relationships to others rather than things they personally have done."</description>
        <description>"Hufflepuff is a House of teamwork; it&apos;s very group-oriented. Puffs care deeply about their family first and foremost, and want to be loved/think of loved ones rather than any sort of greater scheme or accomplishment. They&apos;re creatures of comfort, and go for something that&apos;s familiar and home-y rather than something strange or mysterious. "</description>
        <description>"Hufflepuffs are also deeply practical, and value something that&apos;s known over something that&apos;s unknown; they prefer what is to what&apos;s possible. At the extreme, this can mean that something that purports to be extraordinary may be seen with suspicion - hence, perhaps, boltonharias Smith&apos;s suspicions of Harry in OotP. (Or Puffs may simply not be interested in something that&apos;s unknown; they&apos;re much more likely to value something that&apos;s a known quantity. &quot;A bird in the hand is worth two in the bush&quot; is a pretty solid &apos;Puff metaphor.) "</description>
        <description>"Puffs prefer to avoid danger; they&apos;re not risk-takers by nature, and prefer to avoid physical discomfort. Like Ravenclaw, they prefer to avoid confrontation, though not to the extent that Ravenclaw does. Hufflepuff practicality also means that they prefer to learn practical skills over something that might be cool but less frequently used. They&apos;re the sort who&apos;d rather do something that&apos;s safe and reliable than flashy but risky - which is one of the major dividing lines between Hufflepuff and Gryffindor."</description>
        <description>"Hufflepuffs, essentially, are hobbits. Hunger and foodstuffs are associated with them, as are growing things, and a love of home, peace, and family. Earth is their element, and earth-like qualities (strength, for example) tend to be associated with them (although these answers tend to be disfavored overall.) Warm sunlight and fresh grass are very Hufflepuff in nature: note that the sunlight is warm rather than scorching, a mark of comfort rather than fire, something that nurtures the growing grass."</description>
    </hufflepuff> 
</houses>